Seward, Ralph T. Papers 5328
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series II: Arbitration Cases, International Harvester
  - IHC - Federal Labor Union, Local 22631 - Milwaukee Case, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - IHC - Canton Works - Local 233 Decision No. 196 - Case FE-257, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 104 Decision No. 195 - Case EM-14024, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - IHC - Farmall Works - Local 109 Decision No. 177, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - IHC - McCormick Twine Mill - Local 141 Decision No. 176 - Case 808 & 809-McT, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - IHC - Eat Moline Works - Local 104 Decision No. 175 - Case 14469. 15025, 14472-EM, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - IHC - West Pullman Works - Local 107 Decision No. 174 - Case 153-50-WP, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - IHC - Tractor Works - Local 101 Decision No. 157, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - IHC - West Pullman Works - Local 107 Decision No. 173 - Case 28-51-WP, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 108 Decision No. 149 - Case No. 5803-McC, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 108 Decision No. 172 - Case 5806-McC, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - IHC - Tractor Works - Local 101 Decision No. 171 - Case 50-14-2(670), 1951 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - IHC - Tractor Works - Local 101 Decision No. 170 - Case No. 50-56-6(649)-T, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - IHC - Tractor Works - Local 101 Decision No. 169 - Case No. 132-T, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - IHC - Tractor Works - Local 101 Decision No. 168 Case 50-7-1(597)-T, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - IHC - West Pullman Works - Local 161 Decision No. 167 - Case 30-50-WP, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - IHC - Tractor Works - Local 101 Decision No. 166 - Case 51-G-2(713)-T, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - IHC - Farmall Works - Local 109 Decision No. 165 - Case 11515-F, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - IHC - East Moline Works,- Local 104 Decision No. 164 - Case 14535-EM, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 104 Decision No. 163 - Case No. 15120-EM, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - IHC - Farmall Works - Local 109 Decision No. 15315-F, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - IHC- East Moline Works - Local 104 Decision No. 161 - Case No. 15309-EM, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - IHC - Louisville Works - Local 236 Decision No. 160 - Case No. 5275-A, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 104 Decision No. 159 - Case No. 11756-EM, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 104 Decision No. 158 - Case No. 15315-EM, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - IHC - Richmond Works - Local 118 Decision No. 156 - Case 1018(11054)-R, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - IHC - West Pullman Works - Local 107 Decision No. 155 - Case No. 140-5-WP, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 104 Decision No. 154 - Case No. 13015-EM, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - IHC - McCormick Twine Mill - Local Decision No. 116 - Case 772-McT, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - IHC - West Pullman Works - Local 107 Decision No. 153 - Case 160-49-WP, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - IHC - Tractor Works - Local 101 Decision No. 152 - Case 48-25-13(293), 1951 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 108 Decision No. 151 - Case 5730-McC, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - IHC - McCormick Twine Mill - Local 141 Decision No. 150 - Case No. 792-McT, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 148 Decision No. 148 - Case No. 5480-McC, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 202-A Decision No. 147 - Case No. 14-McC, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 108 Decision No. 146 - Case 5483-McC, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - IHC - West Pullman Works - Local 107 Decision No. 145 - Case 115-49-WP, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - IHC - Tractor Works - Local 101 Decision No. 144 - Case 48-25-15(296), 1951 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 108 Decision No. 118 - Case No. 5511-McC, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - IHC - West Pullman Works - Local 161 Decision No. 143 - Case 7-48-WP, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - IHC - Richmond Works - Local 118 Decision No. 142 - Case C-8(1503) -R, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - IHC - Richmond Works - Local 118 Decision No. 141 - Case 1450-R/K-7, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - IHC - Louisville Works - Local 236 Decision No. 140 - Case 3782-A, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - IHC - Richmond Works - Local 118 Decision No. 139 - Case 1479-R/B-53, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - IHC - Richmond Works - Local 118 Decision No. 138 - Case 1483-R/B-57, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - IHC - Richmond Works - Local 118 Decision No. 137 - Case 1497-R/E-17, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - IHC - Richmond Works - Local 118 Decision No. 136 - Case 1494-R-G-6, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - IHC - Louisville Works - Local 236 Decision No. 135 - Case 5114-A-L, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - IHC - Louisville Works - Local 236 Decision No. 134 - Case 3562-A-L & 3563-A-L, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - IHC - Tractor Works - Local 182 Decision No. 133 - Case 48-22-Acc. 12-T, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - IHC - East Moline Works Local 156 Decision No. 132 - Case No. 0-2A-EM, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - IHC - Farmall Works - Local 109 - Decision No. 131 - Case 23667-F, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - IHC - Farmall Works - Local 109 Decision No. 130 - Case 4928-F, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - IHC - Farmall Works - Local 109 Decision No. 129 - Case No. 23202-F, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 104 Decision No. 128 - Case No. 11654-EM, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - IHC - Farmall Works - Local 109 Decision No. 127 - Case No. 16349-F, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - IHC - Farmall Works - Local 109 Decision No. 126 - Case No. 23514-F, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - IHC - Richmond Works - Local 118 Decision No. 125 - Case No. 1079-R-8, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 104 Decision No. 124 - Case No. 12358-EM, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 104 Decision No. 123 - Case No. 14765-EM, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - IHC - West Pullman Works - Local 107 Decision No. 122 - Case No. 65-50-WP, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - IHC - West Pullman Works - Local 107 Decision No. 121 - Case No; 13-50-WP, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 108 Decision No. 120 - Case 5595-McC, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - IHC - West Pullman Works - Local 107 Decision No. 119 - Case 52-50-WP, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - IHC - Farmall Works - Local 109 Decision No. 117 - Case 18939 - F, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 108 Decision No. 115 - Case No. 5565-McC, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 108 Decision No. 114 - Case No. 5527-McC, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 108 Decision No. 113 - Case No. 5564-McC, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - IHC - McCormick Twine Mill - Local 141 Decision No, 112 - Case No. 731-McT, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - IHC - West Pullman Works - Local 107 Decision No. 111 - Case 16-50-WP, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - IHC - McCormick Twine Mill - Local 141 Decision No, 110 - Case No. 707 - McT, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - IHC - Tractor Works - Local 182 Decision No. 109 - Case 49-3-PLG-T, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - IHC - Louisville Works - Local 236 Decision No. 108 - Case 6451-A & 6452-A, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 108 Decision No. 107 - Case 4638-McC-5 4693-McC-6, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 104 Decision No. 106 - Case No. 15551-EM, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - IHC - Richmond Works - Local 118 Decision No. 105 - Case No. 1178-R, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - IHC - Richmond Works - Local 118 Decision No. 104 - Case No. 878-R, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - IHC - Richmond Works - Local 118 Decision No. 103 - Case No. 481-R, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - IHC - Louisville Works - Local 236 Decision No. 102 - Case No. 4473A-1, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - IHC - Louisville Works - Local 236 Decision No. 101 - Case No. 4699-A-L, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - IHC - Louisville Works - Local 236 Decision No. 100 - Case No. 4316-A-L, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - IHC - Louisville Works - Local 236 Decision No. 99 - Case No. 5146-A-L, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 104 Decision No. 98 - Case No. 14809-EM, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - IHC - McCormick Twine Mills - Local 141 Decision No. 97 - Case No. 749, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - IHC Louisville Works - Local 236 Decision No. 96 - Case No. 4516-A-L, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - IHC - Farmall Works - Local 109 Decision No. 95 - Case No. 15296-F, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 202a Decision No.94 - Case No, 11-McC-18, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 104 Decision No. 93 - Case 12868-EM, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 104 Decision No. 92 - Case No. 12880-EM, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 104 Decision No. 91 - Case No. EM-12628, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - IHC - Auburn Works - Local 180 Decision No. 90 - Case No. 352, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 108 Decision No. 89 - Case 5013-McC-8 5044-McC-7, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 156 Decision No. 88 - Case No. 0-77-EM, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - IHC - Richmond Works - Local 118 Supplemental Award Decision No. 87 - Case No. 7003-R-4, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 104 Decision No. 86 - Case No. 11652-EM, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 156 Decision No. 85 - Case No. 0-79-EM, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - IHC - Farmall Works - Local 109 Decision No. 84 - Case Nos.6224, 16078 & 26959-F, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - IHC - Canton Works - Local 233 Decision No. 83 - Case No. FE-176-C, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - IHC - Canton Works - Local 233 Decision NO. 82 - Case No. FE-274-C, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - IHC - Farmall Works - Local 109 - Decision No.81 - Case No, 22034-F, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - IHC - Tractor Works - Local 182 decision No. 80 - Case 48-8-Acc.-T-13, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - IHC - West Pullman Works - Local 107 Decision No. 79 - Case 157-49-WP-11, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - IHC - Tractor Works - Local 101 Decision No. 78 - Case 48-25-12(292), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - IHC - West Pullman Works - Local 107 Decision No. 77 - Case 149-49-WP-10, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - IHC - Louisville Works - Local 236 Decision No. 76 - Case 656A-L-10, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - IHC - Tractor Works - Local 101 Decision No. 75 - Case 49-56-3 (365), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - IHC - Tractor Works - Local 101 Decision No. 74 - Case No. 498-T-10, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 108 Decision No. 73 - Case No. 5144-McC-15, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - IHC - Louisville Works - Local 236 Decision No. 72 - Cases 129-130-131-164-L-12, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 108 Decision No. 71 - Case 5199-McC-17, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - IHC - Auburn Works - Local 180 Decision No. 70 - Case No. 770, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 104 Decision No. 69 - Case 10539-EM-7, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - IHC - Canton Works - Local 157 Decision No. 68 - Case 24-2689-C-7, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - IHC - Auburn Works - Local 180 Decision No. 67 - Case No. 719, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - IHC - Louisville Works - Local 236 Decision No. 65 - Case 3838A-L-11, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - IHC - McCormick Twine Mills - Local 141 Decision 66 - Case No. 738, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - IHC - Richmond Works - Local 118 Decision No. 64 - Case 2023-R-6, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - IHC - West Pullman Works - Local 107 Decision No. 63 - Case 175-48-WP-7, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - IHC - Richmond Works - Local 118 Decision No. 62 - Case 12003-R-3, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - IHC - Richmond Works - Local 118 Decision No. 61 - Case 2036-R-9, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - IHC - Farmall Works - Local 109 Decision No. 60 - Case No.. 8507-F-5, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - IHC - Farmall Works - Local 109 Decision No. 59 - Case No. 14055-F-6, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - IHC - Louisville Works - Local 236 Decision No. 58 - Case 4263A-L-7, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - IHC East Moline Works - Local 156 Decision No. 57 - Case No. E-330, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - IHC - Louisville Works - Local 236 Decision No. 56 - Case No. 1567A-L-8, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - IHC - Louisville Works - Local 236 Decision No. 55 - Case 2311 1/2A-L-9, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 104 Decision No. 54 - Case 1267-EM-8, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - IHC - Louisville Works - Local 236 Decision No. 53 - Case 2474-A-L-6, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 108 Decision No. 52 - Case 5087-McC-14, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 108 Decision No. 51 - Case 5039-McC12, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 108 Decision 50 - Case Np. 5069-McC-13, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 108 Decision No. 49 - Case No. 5044-McC-7 5013-McC-8, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 108 Decision No. 48 - Case No. 5058-McC-9, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - IHC - Richmond Works - Local 118 Decision No 47 - Case No. 7003-R-4, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - IHC - Canton Works - Local 233 Decision No. 46 - Case No. 229, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - IHC - Canton Works - Local 233 Decision No. 45 - Case No. 255, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - IHC - Tractor Works - Local 101 Decision No. 44 - Case No. 334-T-1 (48-32-3), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - IHC - Canton Works - Local 157 Decision No. 43 - Case No. 19-3963-C-6, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 104 Decision No. 42 - Case No. 17453-EM, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 156 Decision No. 41 - Case No. 0-63-EM, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - IHC - Farmall Works - Local 109 Decision No. 40 - Case No. B-342, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 156 Decision No. 39 - Case No. 0-33-EM, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - IHC - Canton Works - Local 157 Decision No. 38 - Case No. 1-3678-C-5, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - IHC - West Pullman Works - Local 107 Decision 37 - Case No. 203-48-WP-8, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - IHC - West Pullman Works - Local 161 Decision No. 36 - Case No. 2-49-WP-6, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - IHC - Tractor Works - Local 101 Decision No. 35 - Case Nos. 354-T-4 357-T-5, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - IHC - Tractor Works - Local 182 Decision No. 34 - 14B-Production-T-6, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 108 Decision No. 33 - Case No. 5086-McC-11, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 202 Case No. 63-McC-5 - Decision No. 32, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 104 Case No. 12571 - Decision No. 31, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - IHC - Farmall Works - Local 109 Decision No. 30 - Case No. B-338, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 203 Decision No. 29 - Case No. 59-A-McC-6, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 203 Decision No. 28 - Case No. 167-McC, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - IHC - West Pullman Works - Local 161 Decision No. 27 - Case No. 38-48-WP-4, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - IHC - West Pullman Works - Local 107 Decision No. 26 - Case No. 39-49-WP-2, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - IHC - West Pullman Works - Local 107 Decision No. 25 - Case No. 40-49-WP-3, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - IHC - West Pullman Works - Local 107 Decision No. 24 - Case No. 28-49-WP-1, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - IHC - West Pullman Works - Local 161 Decision No. 23 - Case No. 88-48-WP-5, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - IHC - Louisville Works - Local 236 Decision No. 22 - Case No. 3013 1/2-A-L-5, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - IHC - McCormick Works - Local 203 Decision No. 21 - Case No. 170-McC-1 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - IHC - Richmond Works - Local 118 Decision No. 20 - Case No. 3012-R-1, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - IHC - Louisville Works - Local 236 Decision No. 19 - Case No. 1731-A-L, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 104 Decision No. 18 - Case No. 17453, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - IHC - Louisville Works - Local 236 Decision No. 17 - Case No. 953-A-L, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - IHC - Richmond Works - Local 118 Decision No. 16 - Case No. 2087-R, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 104 Decision No. 15 - Case No. 12215, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - IHC - Farmall Works - Local 109 Decision No. 14 - Case No. B-337, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - IHC - East Moline Works - Local 156 Decision No. 13 - Case No. 0-21, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - IHC - Canton Works - Local 157 Decision No. 12 - Case No. 17-3159-C, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - IHC - Auburn Works - Local 188 Decision No. 11 - Case No. 1768-A, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - IHC - Auburn Works - Local 180 Decision No. 10 - Case No. 1601-A, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - IHC - Auburn Works - Local 188 Decision No. 9 - Case No. 4390-A, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - IHC - Tractor Works - Local 182 - Decision No. 8 - Case No. 48-20-MFG, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - IHC - Farmall Works - Local 156 - Decision No. 7 - Case No. 10962, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - IHC - Louisville Works - Local 236 Decision No. 6 - Case No. 673-A-L, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - IHC - Louisville Works - Local 236 - Decision No. 5 - Case No. 930-A-L, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - IHC - Auburn Works - Local 180 Decision No. 4 - Case No. 1076-A, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - IHC - Canton Works - Local 157 - Decision No. 3 - Case No. 3-3070-C, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - IHC - Canton Works - Local 233 - Decision No. 2 - Case No. FE-227-C, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - IHC - Canton Works - Local 233 - Decision No. 1 - Case No. 180-C, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- Series III: Arbitration Cases, Railroad
  - Brotherhood of Firemen; Folder 1, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Use of Firemen on Other than Steam Power Consist of Read and Yard Crews, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen - Safety Awards Program, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Use of Firemen on Other than Steam Power Consist of Road and Yard Crews, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Analysis and Evaluation of Carriers' Exhibit 49 Study of Work Performed By Firemen-Helpers, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Reference Book Award of Arbitration Board 282, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Reference Book Award of Arbitration Board 282 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - 'Before the Arbitration Board', 1963 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Dispute between Carriers Conference Committees and Certain of their Employees, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Dispute between Carriers Conference Committees and Certain of their Employees; Folder 2, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Dispute between Carriers Conference Committees and Certain of their Employees; Folder 3, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Dispute between Carriers Conference Committees and Certain of their Employees; Folder 4, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Study of Crew Consist Requirements Southern Pacific Company, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Trainmen Charts, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Before the Arbitration Board, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Brotherhood of Firemen, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Brotherhood of Firemen, Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Bdx 9,10,11+12, 1959-1963 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Statement of Supervisors of Enginemen Proving Essentially of Firemen-Helpless, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - 'Before the Arbitration Board', 1963 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Developments Following the Report of the Presidential Railroad Commission, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - The Diesel Rules Movement (Volume 2 1949-1954), 1963 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - National Labor Arbitration Board; Volume 23, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - National Railway Labor Arbitration Board; Volume 27, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - National Railway Labor Arbitration Board; Volume 28, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - National Railroad Labor Arbitration Board; Volume 29, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - National Railway Labor Arbitration Board; Volume 15, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - National Railway Labor Arbitration Board; Volume 25, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - National Railway Labor Arbitration Board; Volume 26, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - National Railway Labor Arbitration Board; Volume 24, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - National Railway Labor Arbitration Board; Volume 20, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - National Railway Labor Arbitration Board; Volume 19, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - National Railway Labor Arbitration Board; Volume 18, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - National Railway Labor Arbitration Board; Volume 17, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - National Railway Labor Arbitration Board; Volume 16, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - National Railway Labor Arbitration Board; Volume 21, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - National Railway Labor Arbitration Board; Volume 22, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Engine Service Employees by Occupation and Age Group, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Before the Arbitration Board; Use of Firemen on Other than Steam Power Consist of Road and Yard Crews - Folder 1, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Before the Arbitration Board; Use of Firemen on Other than Steam Power Consist of Road and Yard Crews - Folder 2, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Before the Arbitration Board; Use of Firemen on Other than Steam Power Consist of Road and Yard Crews - Folder 3, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Manning of Railroad Motive Power and Trains in Countries other than the United States and Canada, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - The History of the Efforts of the Firemen's Organization to Force the Employment of Firemen on other than Steam Power, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - The Diesel Rules Movement (Volume I-1933 to 1949), 1963 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Railways of Latin America, Indo-Asia, Africa, Australia, and European Illustrations, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Before the Arbitration Board, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - The Essentiality of the Fireman-Helper Part 2, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Before the Arbitration Board - 'Use of Firemen..', 1963 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Collective Bargaining on Manning Rules and Current Railroad Accident Record, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Progress Report 1962; Parts and Rebuild Seminar (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Statement of Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen Regarding Controversies as to Meaning or Application of the Award, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Rebuttal to Testimony and Motion Pictures, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Reference Book Award of Arbitration Board 282, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - N.M.B., 1963 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Assoc of Railway Trainmen and Firemen and International Association of Railway Employees, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Forms - Certif., 1960 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Joint Press Release, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Union Railway - Florida East Coast, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Index - Carriers (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Arbitration Board, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - CRX-9B and 9A, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Statistics, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Grievance No. D-1081, 1953-1954 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers and Firemen, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Reports of the Presidential Railroad Commission, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Arbitration, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - 'Before the Arbitration Board' Folder 1, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - 'Before the Arbitration Board' Folder 2, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - 'Before the Arbitration Board' Folder 3, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - 'Before the Arbitration Board' Folder 4, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - 'Before the Arbitration Board' Folder 5, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 18)